Kushagra Shrivastava

Discord: @protonicgod Website: protonicgod.me

Description

I am Kushagra and I go by Protonicgod, I am a seasoned Discord Community Manager with over 4 years of experience specializing in community moderation and management. I have worked with brands and content creators with over 20,000,000 followers. Being the owner of India's largest advertisement server, I am committed to use my experience to build and nurture thriving communities whilst promoting growth.

Experience

Associate Community Manager

Feb 2023 - Present

ModSquad (Feb 2024 - Present): Spearheaded the development of highly engaged online communities for leading multinational tech companies. Conducted in-depth research to identify potential community partners and collaborated with cross-functional teams to enhance user experience, driving significant community growth. Successfully managed communities with up to 1,000,000 members.

Discord Community Manager

- Sept 2019 Present
 - Makeshift Project (May 2024 Present): Created and managed with the Makeshift Project (1.3 million on Youtube) on their official Discord server for their fans.
 - Code Social (May 2023 Present): Grew community membership from 300 to 1,200 members in 5 months (300% growth) and implemented effective strategies to attract and retain new members.
 - Sponic Advertisements (June 2022 Present): Owner of India's biggest advertisement server (13,000).
 Managed a team of moderators and other teams to keep the server running smoothly and provide a positive experience for all users.
 - Battlechest (Dec 2023 May 2024): Oversaw the successful coordination and execution of gaming tournaments for a thriving 16,000-member community. Introduced three over-the-top programs for community, which promote healthy lifestyle habits including reading.
 - Jobs, Hiring & Market (Oct 2023 Mar 2024): Managed one the biggest freelancer platforms on Discord
 with over 11,000 members. Successfully revamped the server to automize the job postings as well as verified reports
 regarding scams.
 - E-Girls Social (Sept 2023 Nov 2023): Mentored and trained new moderators, passing on knowledge and skills to help them succeed in their roles in the large and hyperactive community (200,000 members).

Discord Community Moderator

Sept 2019 - Present

- ♦ Sexy.AI (Sept 23 Present, 19,000 members): A leading NSFW AI image generation platform.
- BeluGANG (Aug 22 Sept 22, 700,000 members): Official Discord server of Beluga, content creator with 10.000,000 followers.
- Hideout (May 22 Jun 22, 135,000 members): One of the most famous and active Discord servers.
- ⋄ Slogo (Aug 21 Apr 22, 300,000 members): Official Discord server of Slogo, or Slogoman, a gaming content creator with over 11,000,000 followers.

EDUCATION

Samrat Ashok Technological Institute

Bachelor of Technology in Internet of Things (IoT)

Vidisha, India

Email: recruitkushagra@gmail.com

Linkedin: iamkushagrashrivastava

Skills

Discord, Notion, ClickUp, Asana, Slack, Adobe Suite (Photoshop, Premiere Pro, After Effects, Audition), Google Workspace (Sheets, Docs, Slides), Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel, Powerpoint)